[Music]
trick
or trick
[Applause]
[Music]
or
Mindy what are you even supposed to be
you're just wearing a bikini can't you
tell bro obviously she's going as a
pumpkin no I'm a dirty Halloween [__]
I'm going as myself for the ninth year
in a
row on the bright side her face sure is
carry enough as it
is good one [__] oh I don't even know
why I hang out with you all you do is
Bully my ass shut your mouth to us
you're just a walking sack of boobies
yeah well what about you Sonic I don't
think I've ever seen the skeleton with
so much meat on it baby don't make fun
of our brother yeah only we can make fun
of you
[__] if I don't dress like this daddy
gets mad at me and that's our problem
[__] that's right you need to shut the
[__]
up Tri
treat damn Heidi you smell good like
Bush's Baked Beans you want some yummy
toothy rolls [__] I got some in my
tights under my crotch for your mouth I
don't really like toy rolls don't care
come inside so we can [__] I have a
boyfriend okay sorry I didn't realize
[__] this
place that's the fourth house and a
robots handed out nothing but to rolles
let's just cross the street and head on
over to another
neighborhood yeah let's make lucky and
piss off but mama says we are not
allowed I don't want to lose my good
girl
[Music]
card fart leby my sexual Master have you
come to trick or treat with me and my
friends [__] we've been through this I
refuse used to participate in the poor
man's holiday you call
Halloween I have been driving around all
night laughing at people who grel for
sweets and I have come to do the very
same to you J Willers Jared you look so
good in your brand spanking Peter Pan
costume I would give the world for you
to spank me right now on my black ass
and make all of the pixie dust fall like
I was covering this here sidewalk with
magical diarrhea [__]
shut up [__] I wish my Paul was around
to see me though he loves Halloween it
was the only time of year he could
follow kids around in a mask and not get
told to stop I miss him too J he really
knew how to give the [__] a real good
time even though he was
103 how about I cheer you up by doing a
little dance I won't even charge you
nothing
poor Jared he hasn't been the same since
he lost his dad yeah he has so little
left to live for now you mean besides
going to town on Kake up hill Billy
[__] I wish there was a way we could
cheer him
up oh huh but perhaps there is what do
you mean well [__] your mother
harnesses the power of magic does she
not have you ever tried asking her if
she could bring your friend's Daddy back
back from the dead art leby you're a
genius of course how come we never
thought of
that Mama Mama we need to ask you a
question what can you use your Royal
magic to bring our friend Jared's dad
back to life [__] no magic is a tool to
be used for the advancement of a better
world to cement this fact casters
throughout time had only two rules you
can't a one individual in their own
personal greed or help Hill
billies okay never mind then guess it's
over if only there was somebody else we
knew who could use magic yeah if only
wait a second actually there is what
about Flora remember when she used that
spell in the emerald Peninsula to blast
robot Nick sleep and dingo off her
land
[Music]
done I have her on speed dial I'll just
call her up right
now why is her name above
[Music]
mine hello wow that was fast sorry I got
a little exed no one has ever called me
before is there something you needed to
say you know we could have met in person
for this I was wondering if you could
raise the souls of the Dead witchcraft
I'm hanging up Flora
wait Sonia I swear to God in hell oh no
oh yes [__] you better not be calling
other magic casters after I told you
know well if your mom is getting
involved this must be very important
while that you you go Flora wait damn it
Sonia Miss Hedgehog it's okay there's
nothing to worry about whatever fear you
have about me may as well have already
been qued I shed the trappings of my
blue person Heritage long ago in favor
of adopting the mannerisms of the
superior white class it's no wonder
Iceland Remains the most peaceful
country in the
world I know baby what about your sex
Uncle if our uncle chuck could use magic
don't you think we would have seen it
already lame [__] sh I'm sorry for
trying to help you're no help at all
don't you got a salad to eat somewhere
you dumb [__] my bro only keeps you
around cuz he likes looking at
knockers well we might as well go see
the old man cuz I ain't see any other
[__] choice we
got hey Bartleby mind giving us a the
ball and his pants is so hot I just want
to S the way back you could drop us off
at the first class neighbor neighborhood
and let you dirty my seats with your
middle class bums alter the no but you
can walk beside my limousine as I drive
slowly so people may get the idea that
we are acquaintances yet not close
enough for people to think I know you
enough to give you a ride Man Sonic your
boyfriend Bart leby really is the
coolest
guy young Master forgive me for dunking
on your boyfriend and his Pals but
surely you don't intend me to actually
drive next to those ass hats We Are Men
of status we do not mingle with
dependent
citizens Alfred put the pedal to the
metal and floor this be we're
here huh so on new [__]
weeds yeah I love having money oh my
[__] God I love it so much the whole
world is my [__] [__] damn Alfred
you got a calm
down this is Uncle Chuck's trailer all
right but where is he and where are all
the scary
decorations that's just a pumpkin you
shoplifted from Kmart and you didn't
even carve
it
yeah
no window open in called can't afford a
space hi Uncle Chuck can we ask you a
question me we were kind of wondering
can you use magic like our mom yeah far
out you mean all this time you could
cast magic spells and you never even
told
us of let turn random objects into an
empty
[Music]
so don't because and not with what about
the other
one well our friend Jared has been
really depressed because his dad died
last year on CH
day we were hoping that if we could
bring his dad back Jared would return to
his happy gol lucky
self he F your pain what you want
Domingo Dumas why not you can literally
bring people back to life what's
stopping
you simply because if you don't get Happ
then please Uncle Chuck we asked Mom and
she said no
please Uncle Chuck it would make us very
happy
NE
an oh
what something is happening to the book
is this the powers of
evil look there was a secret room behind
that bookcase and Uncle Chuck's trailer
all
along ingredi secret
Laboratory
as for the of
you cross into secret Chambers with the
help of this magic circle
so what
for that's all of it now we just have to
put it in the pot right OMG manic it's
called a cauldron don't you know
anything about
Magic first it says here we need to
throw in a couple of of Dragon
[Music]
Eyes next a half a jar of liquid
Moonlight can of budlight specifically
bought before the whole budlight
controversy and as a PL baggie of Uncle
[Music]
chuckp is it
ready the potions looking good uncle
we're ready when you are
splend that how long is this going to
take I want to go home and watch
Halloween Heroes the Hallow classic that
was released in 2021 by JC films that
can be viewed for free on the Roku
Channel bro do you see what I see it's
an angel they really do exist I'm so
excited I just crapped maybe God will
wipe my
butt me
too Amigos
[Music]
so what you want
in see what's happening you don't think
he can be an because I'm
Mexican is that
it no no it's not that then what is
it the host didn't expect
on I'm not going to take this from a
moral if that's how you feel then how
[Music]
about
okay come
back
oh so now you want to talk to me why
don't you tell me why that is look
e not I
am now you have a to with my and is rist
[Music]
against oh no
I am Megatron the voice of God and the
guardian of Heaven's secret records
there is no angel greater than I and no
mortal well besides be CL Tres of course
for what purpose do near Mortals have to
cast a spell of such cruelty and
coldness to call upon my service answer
me quickly before I will Smite you with
the fist of God himself or poop in your
face like you a public toilet that I
will sit upon with my
cheeks don't got anyone like that up
here you might want to check down
below well Jared's dad was kind of a
[__] I let's do it
again or
her
Comm
Uncle Chuck you did it your magic spell
really worked of course I did welcome to
the world of the
living Sonic the Hedgehog your boyfriend
ran over me with a train in my own front
lawn if I so much to see you on my
doorstep again even if it's Christmas
I'm going to blast your brains out with
my
shotgun so that not even a TKS
oh so you want compensation I'll give
you a little something right here before
I go Yeehaw right him
Cowboy have fun scrubbing down the
fireplace to R of my [__] f
it come on let's go find Jared I can't
wait to see his
reaction
what in the world Mindy Nu what happened
to
you yeah why are you guys like 8 years
old all of a sudden blame your stupid
Uncle his damn spell went haywire all
over the [__] house a ocean fell
right on our heads and I almost took a
lightning bolt up the butt me too but
unlike him I was hoping it would go up
my butth hole course that would be
hot can of m
c are you kidding me you did this to us
on purpose this is why I hate hedgehogs
change me back now before I punch you in
the balls you and then I'll suck
them
no return to noral
exactly not it that simply other one who
are you talking about Sonic you got to
see
this what is happening to me I'm turning
invisible Uncle Chuck was I hit by one
of your strace pells or something help
me or I'm telling mama oh yeah
for bring us all
[Music]
from so you chose me mind is standing
right there you are disted
man that sucks when are we going
trick-or-treating list to
[Music]
kids
only
[Music]
then that gives us just under 5 hours to
reach both Taco Bell and Jared's Farm
where p is no doubt hiding out at let's
move gang you expect an adorable
8-year-old kid like me to walk around on
Halloween night without adult
supervision what if I get grabbed by a
molester
it's okay Nu big sis will make sure
nothing bad happens to
you what's that [__] you want me to buy
your uncle a Juna salad sandwich from
Subway why I would love
to how can I order a yummy foot long
wellow you're Bartleby yeah that's right
now don't talk to me I'm ordering a
sandwich can I have an
autograph I'm sort of in the middle of
ordering that's okay I'll wait so what
are you going to get it's some for a
friend who's your friend maybe I know
him what's your yearly Financial
income around 24,000 a
year trust me when I say that we do not
share the same
acquaintances
what do you want I'll take it tuna salad
sub with pickles and no mayo and you
know what what it's my cheat day okay so
throw in some salt and vinegar chips
okay that's not all okay throw in a can
of Pepsi we're all out okay never mind
[Music]
okay here's your tuna salad sandwich did
you put mayo on it I asked for no mayo
my
bad here's your tuna salad
sandwich thank you very much yo what
about My Autograph here's some advice
kid how about rather than idolizing
celebrities which are basically glor F
strangers who will never give you the
time of day learn to love yourself
instead you are the one that matters
most of all
really I matter in fact why don't
instead I have your
autograph Bart leby Monclair of Dres is
asking for My Autograph this is the best
day of my
life Bartleby Bartleby why are you
leaving oh you're still here I was under
the assumption that you knew it was a
joke no one would ever want your
autograph you're
[Music]
worthless
the staer park looks disgusting I not
stepping one foot in there hey old dud
come to the window and hold out your
arms I got you
Subway [__] but super long limousine is
still driving by and across cross the
street is Jed vanon house we'll never
get to the other side like this it's no
use one of us is going to have to crawl
under and get to the other
side I will do it no Blinky you can't
you are manik's best
friend I know and it's because I his
best friend that I am willing to do this
because my name is Blinky my older
brother would Bully Me by calling me
Stinky so I want to prove to the whole
world that I'm not stinky I am Blinky
and if I can go out saving Manic the
Hedgehog my best friend then I would be
hyped as
[__] go Blinky go you can do it just a
little more to go don't give up I'm
making it you guys are you watching I'm
already halfway across I'm going to do
it I'm going to sing arel
manic oh God the end of the limo is here
there's no way he will make it under the
bumper in that cat PR this hurry Blinky
hurry before you get run over you're
going to die if you die oh my God
no not Blinky why did it have to be him
Blinky you've always been there with us
through thick and thin that's right
never wanting to steal the shell just
satisfied being a part of the
crew I will never forget you as long as
eyelids
tiny iose eyes and I can see the day we
met just one moment then I knew you're
my best friend do
anything for you we've gone so far and
done so
much and I feel
feel like we've always been together
right by my side through thick and
thin you're the part of my life I'll
always
remember Sonic I've been meaning to call
y'all you're not going to believe what
happened tonight it's a Halloween
Miracle let me guess it's about your paw
isn't it why how did you know that fat
boy well you see it all started like
this that was a warning shot the next
step you take I'm sending bullet right
through your [__] face boy now get
off my land we don't want no hedgehogs
carrying about Paw stop they white folk
gosh darn it you're lucky my son is
correct sorry Sonic you know how the old
man can be he's been saying some weird
[__] how he came back from the dead
through the powers of evil and how they
might be trying to send him back to the
underworld that's actually what we're
here to talk about with you Jared don't
tell me sorry Jared we wanted to do
something nice for you after we saw you
crying like a little girl but things
didn't exactly go as planned so now we
have to send your bo back to the burning
rivers of hell
no I won't let you take him away from me
Sonic not now that I have him back in my
arms
again a shoot he has a tiny knife like
Peter Pan don't let him es he has to pay
for this a [__] guess I'm going to have
to replace this door frame
again bro you stay here and rest that
ass well go in there and kill that
bastard no bro I started this and so I
deserve it it's it's not wrong for Jared
to be angry with me or for anyone to be
jealous of my cool blasberry
mohawk if we can't convince Port then we
have to find another Necromancer to undo
the spell I'm not going to lose my
boyfriend like this do you hear me baby
man are you even listening to me shut up
[__] how y did I hear someone say they
require the powers of wickedness and
despair if so then I'm your
girl Sarah you're an acancer why sure I
am cutie PTI why do you think I'm
black but why would you ever help us it
was Sonic's boyfriend Bartley who killed
paw and also to yours and Jared's
relationship apart that may be true but
I want to help because he and I are the
same manic is the triplet that nobody
likes and I'm just ugly as [__] I'm like
the westernized version of hearts and
Miku so me and manic in a way are two
P's in a part except and like him I'm
ugly as
[__] Vision hurry and free manic of his
curse so we can get our trick or treat
on unfortunately I don't know any spell
that can undo what your handsome Uncle
did this Hedgehog appears to have had a
mighty powerful incantation placed upon
him even I'm not powerful enough to
remove it entirely
but that's quite fine there is still one
thing I can
do if I move the incantation from manic
and put it onto somebody else your
brother can still be saved and Pa will
be able to live too it would be a
win-win situation but who on Earth would
that be we can't just kill a random
person why will just kill my own mother
she's been a thorn in my side for too
long also I'm on the Wheel to inherit
her [__] bar on house it would be
like wiping two but holes with one
square of toilet paper she's in that
building over there ma lives all by her
lonon because nobody likes her let's
murder
her there you are you filthy [__] did
you get my Burger
King oh you little [__] I see what's
going on here there's an incantation on
that boy and you intend to pass it over
to me well I ain't letting that happen
you hear the barn house will never be
yours I don't think you have a say in
this m shut up where's my Whopper you're
not getting any of that M
why what is the power of ancient evil to
a
shotgun uh
ouch Sarah's in trouble sips we have to
help her it's juice and
[Music]
time now this was what show
down she's still overpowering us is she
using some kind of wind magic she has to
be no she's just [__] partying on us
don't give up she has to stop
[Music]
[Applause]
eventually
[Music]
my
best to never
[Music]
let good job everyone we knocked out the
old
[__] now I can use my magic to transfer
the curse from manic to my mama you
[__] [__] I raised you like my
daughter because you were I knew I
should have made the knot tighter when I
put you in a sack and Fe you in the lake
when you were a baby yeah maybe you
should have bye-bye now mama I'm going
to enjoy my pristine new B
house oh man bro you had us scared half
to death you know I thought I would have
to go look for a new
brother I ain't the only one who made
its onic look out
there come on Paul I hear they're
handing out tootsie rolls on East Street
Tootsie Rolls I haven't had a tosie
since I was a boy now that fat ass of C
I want to smack it a whole
lot
it is
[Music]
done
thank you all for being here today is
most Funeral Service well I guess I
shouldn't be surprised since you're the
ones that killed
her before we all say a few words is
there anything someone would like to add
yes C
Dracula why are we doing this outside in
your front lawn instead of some kind of
a new and why are you in an up house
good question the answer to your second
question is that I have to take a smelly
D and I'm not going to answer the first
one how about that boy okay I don't
really care to be quite honest who else
has a question for my
ass the Indian caricature from that one
racist song in Peter Pan I just want to
get things straight in the 31st episode
of Sonic Underground where Jared Sarah
and all you [__] debuted for the
first time Sarah and Jared were shown to
be in a secret romantic relationship at
the start yes and you're Jared's Dad yes
and Muer's mother yes and at the end of
the episode you and Ma got together in a
romantic relationship
too yes so doesn't that mean Sonic
Underground technically promoted incest
yes I will accept no further
questions me and M didn't always see
things I I you see except for the times
she came over looking to be real in her
smelly ass haha which was a couple of
times a day what I'm trying to say is if
there's anyone who may have a few K
words to share you may do it
now when I walked into that room tonight
and I saw that gun pointed at me all I
could think was damn this [__] is crazy
and what's she going to use that gun for
is she going to [__] shoot
me I have never feared more for my life
than when she demanded a Whopper from
Burger King
she tried to fart on us I could not
believe it when she literally tried to
fart on us it smelled so bad in there I
had to leave the [__]
room I'm going to be honest with you
when
he
that was
import that [__] stole my radishes she
still needs to pay me back preferably
with but six P now's not the time it's
always the time God I loved that [__]
she was ugly as [__] but that dump truck
of her was packing fat load and that's
all man could never want him wi in now I
know Halloween is is almost over but
that doesn't mean the fun has to stop if
you still have time we're hosting a
trunk or treat out front on my Paul's
Farm we would be delighted if y'all came
the admission is $16 and you can take
home three pieces of candy there's also
a barrel where you can go bobbing for
apples and play corn hole if you're into
that [__] and then when we're done we
can get together and watch Halloween
Heroes on the Roku channel for first
thanks for coming to the trunk or tree
guys be sure to come back again next
year for three more j a piece of poo poo
I swear I did not just see you give that
boy three whole pieces of candy give him
a fourth one that boy's Uncle defeated
Battle of the devil and brought me back
from hell I think he earned himself an
extra jitsy
roll
oh my goodness look seed Daisy everyone
Mama came back to us oh this Tinker Bell
is so happy she could Z some Tinker
balls but how is this possible Sarah
transferred the incantation over to you
you dirty [__] you just couldn't stay
away from the sting balls could
you let's just say a good friend offered
to take my place an eternal Dam
nation very is a
world that
is
and it can be so we did it boys we truly
are the H going
Heroes I'm so glad to finally be back
none of this would be possible if it wor
for all of my
friends and how did I forget my best
friend you the one watching this episode
right now thank you so much for coming
along on this adventure we couldn't have
done it without you hey what was your
favorite part of the
[Applause]
episode I like the too so what are you
going to dress up as for
[Music]
Halloween well that sounds really cool I
hope you have it yourself for I feel
Halloween because you deserve it I love
you it can Shadow human
nature and all that we
need is the way to find the
answer and one
sure you can count on us for good here
we are going far to save all that we
love if we give all we've got we will
make it through here we are like a star
shining bright on your world
today make evil go away come your call
we we set it all come your call be there
when you call come we will stand
real stronger after all we'll do our
best to never let you
down we're up to the
test to turn this world
around
here we are going far to save all that
we love if we give all we've got we will
make it through you we are like a star
shining Bri on your world
today make evil good you are to save all
that we love if we give all we've got we
will make it through you we are like a
star shining Bri on the world
today make evil go
[Music]
away uh uh uh uh
and pretty cool stus but can you show us
how to do handstand
first already
show oh it seems we forgot would you
mind showing us again it's what a hero
would
do guess so nothing with put in a bit
more exercising
after exing
and spers what is going on
here
[Music]
iing
stay spiss Z is trying to hack into my
toy car's enertainment system Z's got me
he's got me by my godamn
[Music]
balls [__] you [__] I bought this car
with my H allowance
tast the team to be
soy shut up [__] somebody help
[Music]
[Applause]
me for
you you can
stop
[Music]
no F you
bitching you
[__] shut up [__] you can't hit me
stupid I'm not even there
ha besides you're not the first one to
go up against my ass die in your [__]
[Music]
flip smell y later
[__] curses leoo Warrior kid got away
but at least they got sport the
[Music]
kiss